# THENMOZHI NAGARAJAN

# PROGRAMMER ANALYST

### CONTACT

+91 8675719756 +91 8072543603

thenmozhipnr@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/thenmozhinagarajan/

Udumalpet

#### SKILLS

- SQL
- PLSQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap

-----

#### EDUCATION

B.E- ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING | 2016-2020

Dr.Mahalingam College of Engineering & Technology Graduated with Cumulative GPA- 8.44

## HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE | 2015-2016

Rajalakshmi Genguswamy matric higher secondary school | Percentage- 89.666

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE | 2013-2014

Rajalakshmi Genguswamy matric higher secondary school | Percentage- 97.666

-----

## COURSES

The complete PL/SQL bootcamp - Udemy
The complete Oracle SQL bootcamp- Udemy
The complete web development bootcamp - Udemy
The complete python pro bootcamp- Udemy

# SOFTWARE SKILLS

Visual studio code PyCharm Oracle SQL developer GitHub

#### PROFILE

As a PROGRAMMER ANALYST with 3 years of experience at Sanmina, I have managed SQL databases using DQL, performing DML operations along with TCL to handle and fix various issues & also builded complex SQL queries. Looking ahead, my goal is to continue expanding my skill set and take on challenging projects. I am eager to join a dynamic team where I can contribute my expertise and learn new technologies. I am highly motivated and willing to adapt and learn whatever is necessary to contribute to the success of the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

## PROGRAMMER ANALYST, SANMINA

November 2021 - December 2023

- Analyzed the requirements from user and provided them extracts by building SQL queries which helps user to analyze and verify the date effectively.
- Experienced in writing advance & complex SQL query using Joins and Sub- Queries to obtain data from multiple tables to deliver Data to Business services.
- Worked in data migration using SQL\*Loader where users provide bulk data & this greatly reduces workload for users and improves productivity.
- Worked in PL/SQL for retrieving, manipulating, checking and migrating data sets in Oracle & Sanmina customized tools. It resulted in migrating data sets in a single shot very effectively.
- Mentored juniors of my team and other business persons by providing guidance and helped them improve their skills and productivity.

# **GRADUATE TRAINEE, SANMINA**

November 2020- November 2021

- Worked in Oracle SQL developer to perform DML operations in database to fix issues that occurs in Sanmina web tools & it enabled users to proceed with their process without any issue and delay.
- Handled web applications used in Sanmina & served as Point-of-Contact with clients for issue resolution and bug fixes in several modules.
- Designed & developed notification mail sent to users as part of approval process in web tools like NCMR & iPR/iCAR using HTML & CSS. This greatly helped approvers to approve easily from mail rather than logging into the portal.
- Troubleshoot the SQL queries and get it tested before execution.

### **GIT Projects:**

https://thenmozhi0307.github.io/portfolio/